Agus Randhani

Jalan Seno Raya , Asrama BIN Tower B , Unit Sadewa 111 , Pasar Minggu , Jakarta Selatan Jakarta, Jakarta
085546977506
randhania93@gmail.com

Summary

Ex Mathematic Teacher and Instructor, convenience to work with data and algorithm, I'm currently living in Jakarta, Java. My skills include, but are not limited to: **Node.js**, **Git**, and **Vue/React**, **D3**. I haven't so many experience yet before but i have a programming attitude. I love to learn, i am a perseverance programmer.

Education

Universitas Airlangga

Graduated March 2015

Bachelor's Degree

Study focus on Research Operation and Computation Problem in Math Perspective

Hacktiv8 Enrolled August 2018

Certificate

Learn About Fundamental of Web Development in javascript language, and learn how to built real fullstack apps with several javascript framework and library

Employment History

BMKG Surabaya

August 2014 - December 2014

Data Analyst and Work System Analyst

- Analyze the data through observation.
- Entry data to Ms. Excel, ME-45, ME-48, and WXREV.
- Processing data and sending the data to the server.
- Reported the results of observations in a book.
- Develop a method for managing research systems work efficiently.
- Make the observation guide.

LBB Sinau

March 2015 - September 2016

Instructor

- -Teaches multiple subjects.
- -Average teaching hour is 15 hours per week.
- Understanding and review subjects scope and sequence as well as ongoing curriculum
- Implementing teaching process to ensure students learning with various methods, assessment, resource learning to accommodate students need and uniqueness.

SMP Dharma Wanita 8 Waru

Mathematic Instructor and Administrator

- -Teaches Mathematic Subjects
- -Understanding k-13, and make subject scope and sequence for 7 and 8 grade class
- -Administer all data student in school database and make a report to Dispendik Sidoarjo , and composed , revised , attend a meeting about school BOS report and finance

Freelance November 2017 - Present

Freelance Web Developer

-Freelancing to create some mathematics college student project at first , some technology that i'm use is Java , Spring , Matlab , C++ , to create some project in research operational and artificial intelligence -Create web project using MEAN Stack , and MEVN Stack

Professional Skills

Node.js & Express

Vue.js

HTML CSS

React Redux

Git and Github

Sqlite, Mongodb, Postgres, Firebase
and SQL

Sequelize, Mongoose, Test-Driven

Intermediate
Intermediate
Competent

Competent

Languages

(GCP)

English Proficient **Indonesian** Native

Development (TDD), and Deployment

Projects

I have created some full stack project during bootcamp in pair project, individual work or my personal work, some that not yet deployed can be seen in my github, and some list can be seen in https://bit.ly/2BpGXbh

Publications

Application of cat swarm algorithm for travelling salesman problem (2015), http://repository.unair.ac.id/27936/